Okay, if you're trying to be healthier in this new year,
cutting down sugar, saving some money,
instead of grabbing these pre-mixed drinks
that cost three to four dollars,
has a ton of sugar and calories,
try this drink that has literally 25 calories
and five grams of sugar,
and it costs less than 80 cents each.
So basically it's like a cocktail mixer,
but it's in the form of an instant packet instead.
And each packet can make you a cocktail in just 10 seconds.
Literally all you have to do is add one of these
to sparkling water, add some liquor,
and bam, you're done in 10 seconds.
No prep or messy cleanup.
And it actually tastes so good
because it's made from real dehydrated fruits
and has no artificial coloring.
Okay, and the best part is that there are only 25 calories
and five grams of sugar.
So you can enjoy these guilt free this new year.
And they're vegan and gluten free,
so all your friends can enjoy these.
You can make these anywhere too,
without any mess or prep.
So I love taking this with me camping and traveling.
And they're on sale right now for 40% off,
so that literally comes down to less than 80 cents per packet.